A Guide to the Publicity Photographs of U. S. Senator Hugh Scott, 1958-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- 1969 September 24 "'For the Victor' - Scott embraces his wife today after he was elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority. Scott defeated Senator Howard J. Baker of Tennessee 24 to 19 in a closed door conference." (103c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (103d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (103e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (103f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (104a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (104b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (104c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (104d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (104e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (104f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (105a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (105b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (105c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (105d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (105e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (105f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (106a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (106b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (106c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (106d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (106e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (106f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (107a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (107b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (107c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Reception after Scott is elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority (107d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Scott with Vice President Spiro Agnew (107e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Scott with Vice President Spiro Agnew (107f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Scott with Vice President Spiro Agnew (107g) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Scott with Vice President Spiro Agnew (108a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Scott and wife embrace, copy of photo by staff member (108b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 Scott and wife reading over a congratulatory telegram (108c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 25 Scott in Whip office (candid) (108d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 25 Scott in Whip office (candid) (108e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 25 Scott in Whip office (candid) (108f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 25 Scott in Whip office (candid) (109a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 25 Scott in Whip office (candid) (109b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 25 Scott in Whip office (candid) (109c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 29 Scott and wife embrace, copy of photo (109d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 29 Senator Robert Griffin as Scott instructs in use of the Whip (109e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 4 Senator Scott and President Richard Nixon in White House office (109f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 4 Senator Scott and President Richard Nixon in White House office (110a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 9 Senator Schweiker; Daniel P. Moynihan, Presidential Assistant for Urban Affairs; and Scott on a joint TV program (candids) (110b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 9 Senator Schweiker; Daniel P. Moynihan, Presidential Assistant for Urban Affairs; and Scott on a joint TV program (candids) (110c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 9 Senator Schweiker; Daniel P. Moynihan, Presidential Assistant for Urban Affairs; and Scott on a joint TV program (candids) (110d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 9 Senator Schweiker; Daniel P. Moynihan, Presidential Assistant for Urban Affairs; and Scott on a joint TV program (candids) (110e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 9 Senator Schweiker; Daniel P. Moynihan, Presidential Assistant for Urban Affairs; and Scott on a joint TV program (candids) (110f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 9 Senator Schweiker; Daniel P. Moynihan, Presidential Assistant for Urban Affairs; and Scott on a joint TV program (candids) (111a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 9 Senator Schweiker; Daniel P. Moynihan, Presidential Assistant for Urban Affairs; and Scott on a joint TV program (candids) (111b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 9 Senator Schweiker; Daniel P. Moynihan, Presidential Assistant for Urban Affairs; and Scott on a joint TV program (candids) (111c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (111e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (111f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (112a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (112b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (112c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (112d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (112e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (112f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (113a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (113b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott at breakfast in honor of Wendell Wilkie (113c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott's first day in Minority Leader's office with workmen still refurbishing (candids) (113d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott's first day in Minority Leader's office with workmen still refurbishing (candids) (113e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott's first day in Minority Leader's office with workmen still refurbishing (candids) (113f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott's first day in Minority Leader's office with workmen still refurbishing (candids) (114a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott's first day in Minority Leader's office with workmen still refurbishing (candids) (114b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 8 Scott's first day in Minority Leader's office with workmen still refurbishing (candids) (114c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 October 14 Senators Griffin, Robert Pachwood, and Scott at Polict luncheon (114d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 12 Scott during TV interview for WMAL (114e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 12 Scott during TV interview for WMAL (114f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office (color negative) (114g) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office (color negative) (115a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office (color negative) (115b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office (color negative) (115c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office (color negative) (115d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office (color negative) (115e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office as the House and Senate Republican Leaders confer (116a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office as the House and Senate Republican Leaders confer (116b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office as the House and Senate Republican Leaders confer (116c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office as the House and Senate Republican Leaders confer (116d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office as the House and Senate Republican Leaders confer (116e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 14 Scott and Representative Gerald Ford in Republican Leaders office as the House and Senate Republican Leaders confer (116f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 18 Senators Schweiker, Ralph Tyler Smith, and Scott on a joint TV program (117a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 18 Senators Schweiker, Ralph Tyler Smith, and Scott on a joint TV program (117b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 November 20 Scott's office mail room showing average of 1500 letter per day (117c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December Informal headshots with a pipe, made after reception for Pennsylvanian congressmen (117d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December Informal headshots with a pipe, made after reception for Pennsylvanian congressmen (117e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December Informal headshots with a pipe, made after reception for Pennsylvanian congressmen (117f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December 15 Senator Schweiker; George W. Romney, Secretary of Housing and Urban Development; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (117g) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December 15 Senator Schweiker; George W. Romney, Secretary of Housing and Urban Development; and Senator Scott on a joint TV program (118a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December 16 Senators Schweiker; Mike Mansfield, Majority Leader; and Scott on a joint TV program (118b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December 16 Senators Schweiker; Mike Mansfield, Majority Leader; and Scott on a joint TV program (118c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December 16 Senators Schweiker; Mike Mansfield, Majority Leader; and Scott on a joint TV program (118d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December 16 Senators Schweiker; Mike Mansfield, Majority Leader; and Scott on a joint TV program (118e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December 17 Scott at the 1776 Commission luncheon (118f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 December 17 Scott at the 1776 Commission luncheon (119a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 Scott with a pipe (candid) (119b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 Scott with a pipe (candid) (119c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 Scott with a pipe (candid) (119d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 January 29 Senators Scott and George Aiken, and Arthur Goldberg (119e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 January 29 Senators Scott and George Aiken, and Arthur Goldberg (119f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 February 2 Scott accepts Missouri ham from Senator W. Stuart Symington, payment of bet on Missouri-Pennsylvania football game (120a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 February 2 Scott accepts Missouri ham from Senator W. Stuart Symington, payment of bet on Missouri-Pennsylvania football game (120b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (120c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (120d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (120e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (120f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (120g) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (121a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (121b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (121c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (121d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (121e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (121f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (122a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (122b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 4 Senator Scott testifying on Senate Foreign Relations in Vietnam (122c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 5 Scott headshot from testifying (122d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 5 Scott headshot from testifying (122e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 9 Senators Scott and Schweiker; and Robert Strausz-Hupe, ambassador to Sri Lanka at hearing on appointment to Senate Foreign Relations (122f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 9 Senators Scott and Schweiker; and Robert Strausz-Hupe, ambassador to Sri Lanka at hearing on appointment to Senate Foreign Relations (123a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 9 Senators Scott and Schweiker; and Robert Strausz-Hupe, ambassador to Sri Lanka at hearing on appointment to Senate Foreign Relations (123b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 10 Senator Schweiker; Richard G. Kleindienst, deputy Attorney General; and Scott on a joint TV program (123c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 10 Senator Schweiker; Richard G. Kleindienst, deputy Attorney General; and Scott on a joint TV program (123d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 10 Senators Scott, Schweiker, and William Saxbe and Kleindienst (123e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 10 Senators Scott, Schweiker, and William Saxbe and Kleindienst (123f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 27 Scott with new pipe (124a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 27 Scott with new pipe (124b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 February 27 Scott with new pipe (124c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 March 6 Scott smoking (candid) (124d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 May 11 Senators Scott and Schweiker at luncheon celebrating 22 nd anniversary of foundation of Israel, Representative Ford giving address (124e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 May 11 Senators Scott and Schweiker at luncheon celebrating 22 nd anniversary of foundation of Israel, Representative Ford giving address (124f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 May 11 Senators Scott and Schweiker at luncheon celebrating 22 nd anniversary of foundation of Israel, Representative Ford giving address (124g) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 April 9 Headshot of Scott (125a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 April 9 Senators Scott and Griffin at Capital Building (125b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 April 9 Senators Scott and Griffin at Capital Building (125c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 14 Scott with John Danforth, Senate candidate from Missouri (125d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 May 11 Senators Scott and Schweiker at luncheon celebrating 22 nd anniversary of foundation of Israel, Representative Ford giving address (126a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 May 11 Senators Scott and Schweiker at luncheon celebrating 22 nd anniversary of foundation of Israel, Representative Ford giving address (126b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 May 11 Senators Scott and Schweiker at luncheon celebrating 22 nd anniversary of foundation of Israel, Representative Ford giving address (126c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 May 15 Scott with group of four witnesses in 1116 (126d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 May 18 Senators Scott and Schweiker with a Pennsylvanian judge at Judiciary Committee (126e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 May 21 Scott with Walter Cronkite of CBS news (126f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 7 Scott smoking pipe (127a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 7 Scott smoking pipe (127b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 13 Scott standing on Reception Room bench to address Rotarian group, Senator Richard Russell, Jr. in doorway (127c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 23 Scott with Leonard Woodcock, the president of United Automobile Workers (127d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 23 Scott with Leonard Woodcock, the president of United Automobile Workers (127e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 28 Close-up headshot of Scott with "I need my job. I'm for Scott." button (127f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 14 Scott with John Danforth, Senate candidate from Missouri (128a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 14 Scott with John Danforth, Senate candidate from Missouri (128b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 14 Scott with John Danforth, Senate candidate from Missouri (128c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 14 Scott with John Danforth, Senate candidate from Missouri (128d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 14 Scott with John Danforth, Senate candidate from Missouri (129a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 Scott embracing his wife (129b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 Scott embracing his wife (129c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 Scott smoking pipe with flag in background (copied from color slide) (129d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 28 Close-up headshot of Scott with "I need my job. I'm for Scott." button (130a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 28 Close-up headshot of Scott with "I need my job. I'm for Scott." button (130b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 July 28 Close-up headshot of Scott with "I need my job. I'm for Scott." button (130c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 August 18 Senators Scott and Proxmire on escalator (130d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 December 31 Senators Scott and Mansfield (130e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1970 December 31 Senators Scott and Mansfield (130f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 2 Senator Scott enjoying a joke with new Senator John V. Tunney after taking his oath of office (130g) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 2 Senator Scott standing by as Senator John V. Tunney takes his oath, administered by Senator Adlai Stevenson III (131a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 2 Senators Scott and Mansfield confer as 91 st Congress comes to a close (131b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 2 Senators Scott and Mansfield confer as 91 st Congress comes to a close (131c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 20 Headshot with Capital in the background from Mansfield-Scott photos (131d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 20 Headshot with Capital in the background from Mansfield-Scott photos (131e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (131f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (131g) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (132a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (132b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (132c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (132d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (132e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (132f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (133a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 21 Scott at his reception after he took oath of office (133b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 January 22 Scott giving an interview after the State of the Union address (133c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 1 Scott holding a press conference on the other side of wall when bomb exploded in Capital building (133d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 1 Representative Gerald Ford and Senators Clifford Hansen and Scott look at damage in men's room, where the bomb exploded (133e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 1 Scott holding a press conference on Capital steps about bomb explosion in Senate wing of the Capital (133f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 1 Scott holding a press conference on Capital steps about bomb explosion in Senate wing of the Capital (134a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 1 Scott and William Hildenbrand, Research Assistant to Republican Leader, inspecting damaged stained glass window in Senate restaurant (134b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 1 Scott and William Hildenbrand, Research Assistant to Republican Leader, inspecting damaged stained glass window in Senate restaurant (134c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 2 Senators Scott, Clinton P. Anderson, Joseph Montoya, and Astronaut Alan B. Shepard, Jr. (134d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 12 Scott conferring with William Hildenbrand (134e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 22 Portrait (134f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 22 Portrait (135a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 22 Portrait (135b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 22 Portrait (135c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 22 Portrait (135d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 March 22 Senators Scott and Clifford Case on a joint TV program (135e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 April 20 Mrs. Hugh Scott, Mrs. Gordon Allott, Mrs. Mike Mansfield, and Mrs. John L. McClellan in Senate dining room for First Lady's luncheon (135f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 3 Portrait (136a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 3 Portrait (136b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 3 Portrait (136c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 3 Portrait (136d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 3 Portrait (136e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 3 Portrait (136f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 3 Portrait (137a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 3 Portrait (137b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 12 Scott holding a press conference outside Capital on way to White House (137c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 May 12 Scott holding a press conference outside Capital on way to White House (137d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 June 15 Senators Scott and Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. on a joint TV program, Weicker shown in monitor (137e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 June 15 Senators Scott and Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. on a joint TV program (137f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 June 15 Senators Scott and Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. on a joint TV program (137g) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 June 15 Senators Scott and Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. on a joint TV program (137h) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 November 9 Senator Scott addresses Policy luncheon (137i) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 November 15 Senators Hugh Scott and Charles H. Percy and Gene Cowan, Treasury official with tax chart (138a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 November 15 Senators Hugh Scott and Charles H. Percy and Gene Cowan, Treasury official with tax chart (138b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 December 4 Scott presides at Senate Judiciary Committee (138c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 December 4 Scott presides at Senate Judiciary Committee (138d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 December 4 Scott presides at Senate Judiciary Committee (138e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 December 4 Scott presides at Senate Judiciary Committee (138f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 December 17 Senators Scott and Mansfield calling President Nixon to inform him that Congress is about to adjourn (they did at 1:32 PM) (139a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 December 17 Senators Scott and Mansfield calling President Nixon to inform him that Congress is about to adjourn (they did at 1:32 PM) (139b) (Box-folder 1:4)